https://www.infinitytools.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Your Privacy & Security, effective October 2018 Infinity Cutting Tools is committed to providing both customers and visitors with the utmost in privacy and security. We abide by all industry guidelines and consistently monitor our management and methods in order to maintain our valued reputation and integrity. This is our promise to our customers, dealers and associates. This privacy statement discloses our privacy practices for www.infinitytools.com for the purpose of demonstrating our commitment to your privacy. Information Collection and UseInfinity Cutting Tools is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Inquiries, Forms and Online TransactionsThe Infinity Cutting Tools Web site is designed to attract customers interested in taking advantage of the great prices and excellent quality of our products. The site has several forms available to our customers and visitors that ask for Personal Identifiable Information. These include Requests for Information, Catalog Requests, Newsletter Subscription, etc. Any information requested by the forms and any future communication resulting from the information disclosed therein shall be directly related to the user's request. The site also has an Online Order Form that enables our customers to place an order online. Infinity Cutting Tools uses SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption when transmitting certain kinds of information, such as credit card payment information. An icon resembling a padlock is displayed on the bottom of most browser’s window during SSL transactions that involve credit cards and other forms of payment. Any time Infinity Cutting Tools asks you for a credit card number for payment or for verification purposes, it will be SSL encrypted. The information you provide will be stored securely on our servers. Once you choose to store or enter your credit card number on Infinity Tools, it will not be displayed back to you in its entirety when you retrieve or edit it in the future. Instead of the entire number, you will only see asterisks and either the first four digits or the last four digits of your number. Personally Identifiable InformationPersonally Identifiable Information is information that can be used to identify a specific user. In the course of filling out an inquiry, requesting a catalog or making a purchase online, you may be asked to disclose Personal Identifiable Information. Infinity Cutting Tools will never collect information from you without your permission. Specifically, you may be asked to provide one or more of the following: Name Postal address Phone number Email address Company name Credit Card Number Providing personally identifiable information is strictly voluntary. It may, however, be necessary for you to provide the information requested in order for Infinity Tools to process your request and or purchase. Whenever a customer or a visitor provides Personal Identifiable Information it will be provided via a secured connection (SSL). VisitorsInfinity Cutting Tools does not require personal information from visitors using our Web site to view our complete line of quality wood cutting tools. NewsletterCustomers and visitors may register to receive our bi-weekly newsletter in order to be notified of new offers and special discounts. When you register for our newsletter certain information will be requested from you to include but not limited to your email address. Your email address will not be shared, sold, rented nor made public (see "Sharing" below). If at any time you do not wish to continue to receive our monthly newsletter, you can opt-out of our newsletter by clicking here and following the instructions. LegalAs a rule, Infinity Cutting Tools will not intentionally disclose personally identifiable information about its Web site users to any third party without first receiving the user's permission. However, Infinity Cutting Tools may disclose personally identifiable information if required to do so by law, or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to, (a) conform to edicts of law or comply with legal process, (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Infinity Cutting Tools, and (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of any user of Infinity Cutting Tools’ products.CookiesWe use "cookies" on our website. Cookies are pieces of information that an Internet site transfers to your hard drive for record-keeping purposes. The use of cookies is an industry standard -- you'll find them almost everywhere on the Internet. Infinity Cutting Tools uses cookies to recognize visitors when they return to our sites. Once we know it's you, we can customize your online visit. For instance, when you are ready to purchase an item, a cookie allows our site to "remember" you have added the item to your shopping cart. We can also show you new products based on your preferences, alert you to new website features, or tell you what new products we have. We may also evaluate our content and services and tailor our websites, for visitors, based on other information we collect such as IP addresses, which are numbers assigned to your computer whenever you use the Internet, pixel tags (or clear gifs), and the type of Internet browser or operating system you are using. This information is collected in the aggregate, but we may tie it to your personal information through cookie use as described above. SharingInfinity Cutting Tools may share aggregated Non-Personally Identifiable Information with our affiliates partners, business partners, and prospective business partners. Such information is shared only for marketing purposes. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person, natural or juridical. The personally identifiable information that you provide to us (such as your name, address and email address) and information about your order may be combined with other personally identifiable information (such as demographic information and past purchase history) available from our records and other sources. This information will be used to make our future marketing efforts more efficient. This information may also be shared with our third party service providers that assist us with our marketing efforts and with other marketers whose products or services we feel may be of interest to you. If you prefer that we do not share your personally identifiable information with other marketers, please email us here. LinksOur Web site contains links to variety of other sites that provide resource information. Please be aware that Infinity Cutting Tools is responsible only for the privacy practices of our Web site. Other Web sites, to which we link, have their own specific privacy policies. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected via Infinity Cutting Tools. Spam ComplaintsInfinity Cutting Tools is 100% permission and opt-in based! If you are receiving e-mails or newsletters from Infinity Cutting Tools you have opted-in to receive such e-mails or newsletters. Spam complaints concerning Infinity Cutting Tools lists are handled with the utmost scrutiny and promptness. If you have received e-mail(s) that you believe to be unsolicited, your e-mail address will be removed from the list to which you were subscribed, and you will not receive any further e-mail correspondence from us, unless otherwise requested in writing. Infinity Cutting Tools upholds its belief in your privacy in order to maintain our valued reputation and integrity. Please note that if you have opted-in to receive information from an affiliate site, you must contact that site directly to be removed from their list. Infinity Cutting Tools Affiliate Partners are prohibited to utilize spam as a marketing tool to promote our products. If you have received unsolicited email from one of our Affiliate Partners we ask that you notify us so that we can take appropriate action. You are welcomed to review our rules regarding affiliates and the use of spam to promote our products. If you have any questions or concerns about anything in this section, please contact us at customerservice@infinitytools.com. SecurityThe Infinity Cutting Tools Web site takes every reasonable precaution to protect our user's information. When you submit information via Infinity Cutting Tools, your information is protected both on-line and off-line in accordance with applicable laws, regulations, and industry standards. For example, without limitation, Infinity Cutting Tools uses a full-time Network Administrator, SSL servers, and 128 bit data encryption to protect the confidentiality of the information you provide. If you have any questions about the security at our Web site, you can send an email to us here.UpdatingCorrecting, updating, or requesting the deletion of information that you have provided may be accomplished by e-mailing us here or by writing Infinity Cutting Tools Privacy Policy, 310 Mears Blvd. Oldsmar, Florida 34677 YouTube Terms of Service We use Youtube to embed videos on our webpage. Please visit YouTube's terms of service here
and also Googles Privacy Policy here.Notification of ChangesInfinity Cutting Tools fundamental commitment to protecting customer privacy will not change. However, regulatory changes or other circumstances may require us to modify this Security and Privacy Statement. In the event that we do amend this statement, it will be posted at www.infinitytools.com/privacy and will be effective 15 days after is it posted. Please note that Infinity Cutting Tools will not change the usage of personally identifiable information collected under a privacy statement without first obtaining express user permission via e-mail. Infinity Cutting Tools’ policy is to use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. If you would like to submit questions or concerns regarding this Security and Privacy Statement, you should e-mail us here or write Infinity Cutting Tools, Security and Privacy Policy, 310 Mears Blvd. Oldsmar, Florida 34677Thank you and enjoy your shopping experience with Infinity Cutting Tools.
Login
Register
Registered Customers
or
Login with Your Social Profile
Login with
Continue with Facebook
or
Forgot Your Password?
Please enter your email address below to receive a password reset link.
Email
Reset My Password
Go back
